chicuu.com 2018-06-29

# Privacy Policy - Chicuu

##  Privacy policy 

Chicuu respects the privacy of every visitor/customer and treats your network safely. Chicuu.com is the sole owner of the information collected on this website, and we interpret our privacy policy as follows: 

##  Privacy Security 

We will not sell, trade or rent personally identifiable information to any person or any company as part of our regular course of business. But you shall also keep your account information safe and do not disclose account information to others.  
How do I unsubscribe?  
You can unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of any email newsletter, or change your subscription settings in your Chicuu user account page.  
Contact us  
If you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy or our processing of your information, please do not hesitate to contact us. 

##  The use of information 

To help us make more convenient for you to use.   
To help us show the most relevant to you.   
To remind you of new information, products with sales, coupons, special promotions and so on.

##  Registration and Order: 

During registration, you will be prompted to provide us with your name, shipping and billing address, phone number, email address and credit card number. These types of personal information are used for billing purposes and to fulfill your orders. If we have problems when processing your order, we may use the personal information you provide to contact you. 

##  Information collected 

  1. The information you provide. 
  2. The information recorded when you browsed. For example, when you use our services, we collect information about which services you use and how you use them. 
  3. Mobile device records, we will collect device-specific information (such as your hardware model, operating system version, unique device identification, and mobile phone information, including phone numbers). 
  4. E-mail communication with the staff of Chicuu. 
  5. Log information, when you use the Chicuu online service or view the contents of Chicuu, we will automatically log your activity and store some information. This includes:  
① Telephone log information such as your phone number, caller number, forwarding number, call time and date, call duration, SMS routing information, and call type.  
② Internet Protocol (IP) address.  
③ Device event information such as a system crash, system activity, hardware settings, browser type, browser language, request date and reference URL.  
④ Cookies that uniquely identify your browser or Chicuu account.  
⑤ Access time 
  6. Location information  
When you use Chicuu online services, we will collect and process information about your actual location. We use various technologies to determine location, including IP address, GPS, and other sensors that may, for example, provide Chicuu with information on nearby devices, Wi-Fi access points, and cell towers. 

##  Information confidentiality 

Your information can only be accessed by our staff, and can only be provided to third parties in the following circumstances:  
With your written permission; or with a Court order.  
You will be notified when your information is likely to be disclosed to a third party.  
Otherwise, you accept Chicuu' terms and conditions so you allow us to use your information in the following circumstances: 

  1. The third party service provider associated with Chicuu: We may hire other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf, such as processing orders, posting packages, sending letters, e-mails or text messages, clearing duplicate information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing help, providing search results and links (including paid search lists and links), handling credit card payments as well as providing customer service. They are able to access customer information to perform their duties, but cannot use this information for any other purpose. 
  2. Business Transfers: For sustainable development of our business, we may sell or acquire platforms, subsidiaries or business units. In these transactions, the customer information is usually part of the assigned business assets, but the information (unless the customer makes some private requirements) is still subject to any previous privacy statement. Although the likelihood is not significant, in extreme cases, customer information should be part of the transferred asset if the site or its affiliates or their respective assets are acquired. 
  3. Schutz dieser Website und anderer. 

##  Related operation license 

  1. Phone  
Chicuu's APP can use your phone/ or its call history. Depending on your voice plan, you may be charged by your carrier for phone calls. Phone access may include the ability to:  
① Write call log (such as call history)   
② Read call log  
③ Reroute outgoing calls   
④ Modify phone state  
⑤ Make calls without your intervention 
  2. Photos/ Media/ File  
Our app can use files or data stored on your device. After obtaining your permission, Photos/Media/Files access may include the ability to:  
① Read the contents of your USB storage (such as SD card).  
② Modify or delete the contents of your USB storage  
③ Format external storage  
④ Mount or unmount external storage 
  3. Local storage  
We may collect and store information (including personal information) locally on your device using mechanisms such as browser web storage (including HTML 5) and application data caches. 
  4. Camera  
You can upload photos when you comment by Chicuu online services. So, we should collect images and other information from your device's camera and photos. For example, you will not be able to upload photos from your camera roll unless we can access your camera or photos. 
  5. Unique application numbers  
Certain services include a unique application number. This number and information about your installation (for example, the operating system type and application version number) may be sent to Newchic when you install or uninstall that service or when that service periodically contacts our servers, such as for automatic updates. 
  6. Cookies and similar technologies  
We use various technologies to collect and store information when you visit a Chicuu online service, and this may include sending one or more cookies or anonymous identifiers to your device. We also use cookies and anonymous identifiers when you interact with services we offer to our partners, such as advertising services or Chicuu features that may appear on other sites.
